Hand me the codes, they're all the same.
A different title for the same old game.
Turn on the keyboard, keep the guitar low.
Just another track for the radio.
It's just the same old song. Another right to
make a wrong.
I'm singing words I don't believe. It's getting
harder and harder to breathe. It's just the same
old song.
I'm dreaming of a feedback whale.
A drunken head like a hammer on a nail
But all I get is this pilot sheet
The safest sound you've ever seen It's just the
same old song Another right to make a wrong
I'm singing words I don't believe. It's getting
harder and harder to breathe. It's just the same
old song.
Is anybody listening? Is anybody real? Or do you
just like the way it feels? It's just the same old
song Another right to make a wrong
I'm singing words I don't believe It's getting
harder and harder to breathe It's just the same
old song The same old song.